#Translated from the zh-CN.yml using google translate and Kelly Mahan

"en":
  login: Login
  register: Register
  how_to_register: How to Register
  logout: Logout
  
  
  
  ################################################ bad translation conversion
    
  
  ################################################ added by localization scripts by: Kelly Mahan
  
  not_to_be_used: "Not to be used"
  features: "Features"
  only_the_use_of_its: "Only the use of its"
  methods: "Methods"
  you_have_not_landed: "You have not landed"
  if_you_do_not_log_calls_when_the: "If you do not log calls when the"
  that_directly_return: "That directly return"
  automatic_processing_of_the_preceding: "Automatic processing of the preceding"
  all_issues: "All issues"
  about: "About"
  search_results: "Search results"
  steering_problem: "Steering problem"
  as: "As"
  according_to_the_present: "According to the present"
  sorting_problem: "Sorting problem"
  did_not_cast_votes_can_not_sort: "Did not cast votes can not sort"
  users_are_invited_to_answer: "Users are invited to answer"
  recommended_topics: "Recommended Topics"
  if_there_is_no_subject_then_set: "If there is no subject, then set"
  the_problem_has_been_sent_to_the_connected: "The problem has been sent to the connected"
  have_the_same_problem: "Have the same problem"
  redirected: "Redirected"
  problems_created_successfully: "Problems created successfully"
  problem_successfully_updated: "Problem successfully updated"
  need_to_filter_out_bad_problem_here: "Need to filter out bad problem here"
  will_answer_the_number_of: "Will answer the number of"
  to_add_the_number_to_answer: "To add the number to answer"
  are_also: "Are also"
  know_almost: "Know almost"
  feedback: "Feedback"
  view_user_not_interested_in_the_problem: "View user not interested in the problem"
  i_block_out_the_problem: "I block out the problem"
  verify_permissions: "Verify Permissions"
  whether_the_user_has_permissions_to_modify_the_development_of_information: "Whether the user has permissions to modify the development of information"
  visitors: "Visitors"
  report_information_has_been_submitted: "Report information has been submitted"
  thank_you: "Thank you"
  up: "Up"
  personal_settings: "Personal Settings"
  topics_cover_upload_successful: "Topics cover Upload successful"
  topics_cover_upload_failed: "Topics cover Upload failed"
  please_check_your_uploaded_images_comply_with_format_requirements_for: "Please check your uploaded images comply with format requirements for"
  answered_question: "Answered question"
  q: "Q"
  problems: "Problems"
  the_question_asked: "The question asked"
  a_topic_of_concern: "A topic of concern"
  concern: "Concern"
  people: "People"
  persons_of_concern: "Following"
  successfully_bound: "Successfully bound"
  account: "Account"
  new_account: "New Account"
  forgot_password: "Forgot password"
  password_mail_message: "This feature will send a special link to retrieve the password to your mailbox"
  login_successful: "Login Successful"
  welcome: "Welcome"
  users: "Users"
  your_account_has_been_created_successfully: "Your account has been created successfully"
  incomplete_account_information: "Incomplete account information"
  landing_can_not_be_directly: "Landing can not be directly"
  please_register: "Please register"
  you_have_not_registered_users: "You have not registered users"
  in_favor: "In favor"
  comments: "Comments"
  you_in: "You in"
  the_answer_to_this_question: "The answer to this question"
  the_answer: "The answer"
  problem: "Problem"
  answer: "Answer"
  a: "A"
  the_problem: "The problem"
  thank_you: "Thank you"
  in: "In"
  answer: "Answer"
  invite_you_to_answer: "Invite you to answer"
  to_ask_you: "To ask you"
  trusted_users: "Trusted Users"
  administrator: "Administrator"
  can: "Can"
  removal_of_the_contents_of_the_area_inside_the_line_marked: "Removal of the contents of the area inside the line marked"
  detect: "Detect"
  over: "Over"
  determine_whether: "Determine whether"
  about_this_answer: "About this answer"
  modify: "Modify"
  anonymous_user: "Anonymous User"
  i: "I"
  he: "He"
  she: "She"
  supporters_list: "Supporters List"
  more: "More"
  welcome: "Welcome"
  be_concerned: "Be concerned"
  skip: "Skip"
  if_the_user_does_not_allow_email: "If the user does not allow email"
  concern_you: "Concern you"
  with_the_new_answer_to_the_problem: "With the new answer to the problem"
  with_the_new_answers: "With the new answers"
  others_invite_you_to_answer: "Others invite you to answer"
  ask_the_user: "Ask the user"
  vote_score_corresponding: "Vote score corresponding"
  supporters: "Supporters"
  there_need_to_add_caching: "There need to add caching"
  sensitive_to_the_word_verification: "Sensitive to the word verification"
  no_help: "No help"
  limit: "Limit"
  one_time: "One time"
  the_default_answer_to_the_concerns_of: "The default answer to the concerns of"
  save_a_list_of_the_user_answered_the_question: "Save a list of the user answered the question"
  last_replied_time: "Last replied time"
  last_active_time: "Last active time"
  this_time_should_be_set_under_the_jurisdiction_of_the_issue_last: "This time should be set under the jurisdiction of the issue last"
  time_of_occurrence: "Time of occurrence"
  redirection_number: "Redirection number"
  asked: "Asked"
  questions_on_the_nominee: "Questions on the nominee"
  finally_an_answer: "Finally, an answer"
  finally_respondents: "Finally, respondents"
  problems_that_can_be_displayed_properly: "Problems that can be displayed properly"
  front_desk_calls_to_bring_this_filter: "Front desk calls to bring this filter"
  except_some_of: "Except some of"
  if_used: "If used"
  incoming_user: "Incoming user"
  question_to_me: "Question to me"
  question_to_a_person: "Question to a person"
  the_default_response_time_for_the_current_time: "The default response time for the current time"
  have_been_easy_to_sort: "Have been easy to sort"
  updated_topics: "Updated Topics"
  parameters: "Parameters"
  can_be_array_or_string: "Can be array or string"
  increase: "Increase"
  remove: "Remove"
  comma_separated: "Comma separated"
  to_both_sides_of_the_space: "To both sides of the space"
  saved_as_a_separate_topic: "Saved as a separate topic"
  submit_a_question_for_the: "Submit a question for the"
  fixed_order: "Fixed order"
  redirection: "Redirection"
  can_not_redirect_their: "Can not redirect their"
  if_the_redirect_target_is_to_redirect_the_present_problem: "If the redirect target is to redirect the present problem"
  to_skip: "To skip"
  prevent_infinite_redirection: "Prevent infinite redirection"
  cancel_redirect: "Cancel Redirect"
  how_many_people_invite: "How many people invite"
  invitation: "Invitation"
  send_email: "Send e-mail"
  insert: "Insert"
  and: "And"
  generated_content: "Generated content"
  detection_of_sensitive_words: "Detection of sensitive words"
  with_sensitive_content: "With sensitive content"
  please_note: "Please note"
  search_store_the_index: "Search store the index"
  three_times_a_query: "Three times a query"
  followed_by: "Followed by"
  arrangement: "Arrangement"
  the_following_two_methods_are_for: "The following two methods are for"
  with: "With"
  upload: "Upload"
  used_to_record: "Used to record"
  is_changed: "Is changed"
  whether_a_woman: "Whether a woman"
  soft_delete_tag: "Soft delete tag"
  that_have_been_deleted: "That have been deleted"
  whether_it_is_trusted_users: "Whether it is trusted users"
  more_trusted_users_to_modify_permissions: "More trusted users to modify permissions"
  not_interested_in_the_problem: "Not interested in the problem"
  concern: "Concern"
  reminded_of_the_state: "Reminded of the state"
  invite_field: "Invite field"
  user_rating: "User Rating"
  temporary_solution: "Temporary solution"
  three_sites_do_not_provide_your: "Three sites do not provide your"
  information: "Information"
  can_not_be_directly_up: "Can not be directly up"
  this_method_is_used_to_process_start_up_automatically: "This method is used to process start up automatically"
  because_no_form: "Because no form"
  automatic_only: "Automatic only"
  if: "If"
  was: "Was"
  is_empty_after: "Is empty after"
  to_use: "To use"
  instead_of: "Instead of"
  prevent_duplication: "Prevent duplication"
  not_interested_in_the_problem: "Not interested in the problem"
  clear_recommended_topics: "Clear Recommended Topics"
  sent_by: "Sent by"
  mail: "Mail"
  thanks_for_replying: "Thanks for replying"
  soft_delete: "Soft Delete"
  just_modify_user_information: "Just modify user information"
  cancelled: "Cancelled"
  my_notifications: "My notifications"
  i_recommend_to_people_or_topics: "I recommend to people or topics"
  refresh_person_recommended: "Refresh person recommended"
  into: "Into"
  delete_the_cache_to: "Delete the cache to"
  information: "Information"
  skip_to_delete_user: "Skip to delete user"
  add_the_right_from_an_array: "Add the right from an array"
  used_to_update_the_time_to_delete: "Used to update the time to delete"
  to_have_a_single: "To have a single"
  there_are_performance_issues: "There are performance issues"
  when_the_query_is_the_user_all_the_items_from: "When the query is the user all the items from"
  to_go_out_there: "To go out there"
  unnecessary_waste_of_memory_transmission: "Unnecessary waste of memory transmission"
  consistent: "Consistent"
  delete: "Delete"
  return_to_the_original_string_format: "Return to the original string format"
  back: "Back"
  format: "Format"
  not_interested_in_obtaining_a_list_of: "Not interested in obtaining a list of"
  not_interested: "Not interested"
  need_to_prevent_duplicate_insertion: "Need to prevent duplicate insertion"
  agree: "Agree"
  sort_will_rise: "Sort will rise"
  against: "Against"
  does_not_display_your_name: "Does not display your name"
  votes: "Votes"
  from: "From"
  add_a_comment: "Add a comment"
  comments: "Comments"
  expressed_appreciation_to_the_respondents: "Expressed appreciation to the respondents"
  thanks: "Thanks"
  and_pertain_to_the_question_that_this_answer: "And pertain to the question that this answer"
  or_no_practical_effect: "Or no practical effect"
  questions: "Questions"
  an_answer: "An answer"
  cancel_concern: "Cancel concern"
  unmasked: "Unmasked"
  number_of_people_to_vote: "Number of people to vote"
  title: "Title"
  text: "Text"
  submit_a_question: "Submit a question"
  or: "Or"
  the_problem_is_added_to_the: "The problem is added to the"
  this: "This"
  topics: "Topics"
  my_home: "My Home"
  my_concern: "My concern"
  recommend_to_my_question: "Recommend to my question"
  my_question_shielding: "My question shielding"
  open_questions: "Open Questions"
  invite_friends: "Invite friends"
  invite_your_friends_to_register: "Invite your friends to register"
  you_may_be_interested_in_the_person_or_topic: "You may be interested in the person or topic"
  home: "Home"
  news: "News"
  see_more: "See more"
  new: "New"
  sharing: "Sharing"
  forwarding_address: "Forwarding address"
  recipient: "Recipient"
  if: "If"
  message_subject: "Message subject"
  to_recommend_to_you_the_problem: "To recommend to you the problem"
  said: "Said"
  to_recommend_to_you_this_question: "To recommend to you this question"
  visiting_address: "Visiting address"
  share: "Share"
  or: "Or"
  close: "Close"
  recommended_text: "Recommended Text"
  you_can_copy_the_contents_of_the_above: "You can copy the contents of the above"
  and_to_forward_it_to_your_microblog_or_send_to_you: "And to forward it to your micro-blog or send to you"
  friends: "Friends"
  they_will_be_able_to_see_this_page_click_on_the_link: "They will be able to see this page, click on the link"
  choose_a_topic_to_this_question_it: "Choose a topic to this question it"
  to_allow_someone_else_to_answer: "To allow someone else to answer"
  search_topic: "Search Topic"
  add: "Add"
  complete: "Complete"
  add_additional_information: "Add additional information"
  add_answer: "Add Answer"
  report: "Report"
  do_you_think_this_is_not_a_problem: "Do you think this is not a problem"
  or_the_answer_can_easily: "Or the answer can easily"
  found_above: "Found above"
  problem_is: "Problem is"
  a_user_that_is_the_problem_after_bad: "A User that is the problem after bad"
  problem_will_be_hidden: "Problem will be hidden"
  bad_question: "Bad question"
  people_think_that: "People think that"
  there: "There"
  an_answer: "An answer"
  you_can_only_answer_one_question: "You can only answer one question"
  but_you_can_modify_the_existing_answers: "But you can modify the existing answers"
  this_problem_is: "This problem is"
  question: "Question"
  only: "Only"
  to_answer: "To answer"
  edit_profile: "Edit Profile"
  submit_answers: "Submit answers"
  this_problem_concerns: "This problem concerns"
  options: "Options"
  another_point_to_a_problem_that_already_exists: "Another point to a problem that already exists"
  the_problem: "The problem"
  point: "Point"
  search_title: "Search Title"
  determine_the_redirection: "Determine the redirection"
  cancel: "Cancel"
  related_issues: "Related issues"
  see_more_related_issues: "See more related issues"
  invite_others_to_answer_this_question: "Invite others to answer this question"
  search_people: "Search people"
  issue_status: "Issue status"
  recent_activity: "Recent Activity"
  viewed: "Viewed"
  times: "Times"
  people_are_concerned_about_the_problem: "People are concerned about the problem"
  created_the_problem: "Created the problem"
  page_does_not_exist: "Page does not exist"
  im_sorry: "I'm sorry"
  the_page_you_requested_could_not_find_us: "The page you requested could not find us"
  topic: "Topic"
  about: "About"
  we_are_a_group_of_programmers_who_aspire_to_a_free_and_open: "We are a group of programmers who aspire to a free and open"
  determined_to_build_an_open_question_and_answer_community_site: "Determined to build an open question and answer community site"
  we_are_happy_to_share_our_project_source_code_and_design_ideas: "We are happy to share our project source code and design ideas"
  for_a_nonprofit_personal_purposes: "For a non-profit personal purposes"
  companies_use: "Companies use"
  team_members: "Team members"
  contributors: "Contributors"
  frequently_asked_questions: "Frequently Asked Questions"
  why_play: "Why play"
  the_name: "The name"
  are_also_updated_every_day_what_to_do: "Are also updated every day what to do"
  code_deploy_and_easy_for_secondary_development: "Code, deploy and easy for secondary development"
  fortunately_than_who_knows_where_almost: "Fortunately, than who knows where almost"
  what_can_change_the_user_name: "What can change the user name"
  who_is_also_a_kind_of_q__a_community: "Who is also a kind of Q & A community"
  welcome_to_those_who_have: "Welcome to those who have"
  here_is_a_variety_to_satisfy_your_curiosity: "Here is a variety to satisfy your curiosity"
  knowledge: "Knowledge"
  discover: "Discover"
  social: "Social"
  desire_to_place_the_discussion: "Desire to place the discussion"
  her_numerous_industries_from_many_parts_of_the: "Her numerous industries from many parts of the"
  people: "People"
  they_proposed_a_variety_of: "They proposed a variety of"
  and_various_organizational_problems_for: "And various organizational problems for"
  composition: "Composition"
  you_can_use_the_search_box_at_the_top_to_try_to_search_for_the_keywords_you_are_interested_in: "You can use the search box at the top to try to search for the keywords you are interested in"
  and_focus_on_some_topics: "And focus on some topics"
  problems_or_who: "Problems or who"
  when_you_look_over_after: "When you look over after"
  you_can_see_these_people: "You can see these people"
  the_dynamic: "THE DYNAMIC"
  you_can_also: "You can also"
  see_you_are_interested_in_new_and_old_problems: "See you are interested in new and old problems"
  sometimes_go: "Sometimes go"
  found_wandering_is_also_a_good_discussion_of_issues_of_interest_and_the_methods: "Found wandering is also a good discussion of issues of interest and the methods"
  or_you_can_go_see_the_more_popular_recent_topics: "Or you can go see the more popular recent topics"
  or_is_it_going_to_those_waiting_for_questions_to_add_some_of_you_know_the_answer: "Or is it going to those waiting for questions to add some of you know the answer"
  you_can_also_look_at_these_hot_issues: "You can also look at these hot issues"
  good_luck_in_your: "Good luck in your"
  happy: "Happy"
  you_may_be_able_to_answer: "You may be able to answer"
  new: "New"
  search_problems: "Search problems"
  member: "Member"
  add_question: "Add Question"
  set: "Edit"
  i_know: "I know"
  a_little_progress_every_day: "A little progress every day"
  blog: "Blog"
  how_to_register: "How to register"
  cooperative_links: "Cooperative links"
  mobile: "Mobile"
  create_new_problems: "Create new problems"
  enter_your_question_here: "Enter your question here"
  optional: "Optional"
  add_more_description: "Add more description"
  add_a_question: "Add a question"
  loading: "Loading"
  report_content: "Report Content"
  please_fill_in_the_reasons_reported: "Please fill in the reasons reported"
  submitted: "Submitted"
  mobile_home: "Mobile Home"
  login: "Login"
  how_to_register: "How to register"
  logout: "Logout"
  regular_edition: "Regular edition"
  background: "Background"
  console: "Console"
  back_to_front: "Back to front"
  notice: "Notice"
  users: "Users"
  hello: "Hello"
  navigation: "Navigation"
  who_is_also_team: "Who is also team"
  from_the_bottom_of_this_message: "From the bottom of this message"
  a_new_q__a_community: "A new Q & A community"
  email_notification_settings: "E-mail notification settings"
  add_the_problem: "Add the problem"
  to: "To"
  issues_raised: "Issues raised"
  modify_the_problem: "Modify the problem"
  modify_a_supplementary_explanation_of_the_problem: "Modify a supplementary explanation of the problem"
  add_the_topic_to_the_problem: "Add the topic to the problem"
  remove_the_subject_from_the_issue: "Remove the subject from the issue"
  the_topic: "The topic"
  thanked: "Thanked"
  concerned_about_the_problem: "Concerned about the problem"
  cancel_the_problem_concerns: "Cancel the problem concerns"
  agree_with_the_answer: "Agree with the answer"
  answered_the_question: "Answered the question"
  changed_their_answers: "Changed their answers"
  as_the_topic: "As the topic"
  the: "The"
  from_the_cover_image: "From the cover image"
  submitted_a_description: "Submitted a description"
  create_a_topic: "Create a topic"
  review_the_problem: "Review the problem"
  new_notifications: "New notifications"
  items: "Items"
  regards: "Regards"
  remove_these_reminders: "Remove these reminders"
  personal_information: "Personal Information"
  personalized_domain_name: "Personalized domain name"
  format_requirements: "Format requirements"
  characters: "Characters"
  can_be_a_letter: "Can be a letter"
  digital: "Digital"
  the_horizontal_line: "The horizontal line"
  if_the_wrong_format_will_be_automatically_processed: "If the wrong format will be automatically processed"
  i_am_a_female: "I am a female"
  email: "E-mail"
  avatar: "Avatar"
  preview: "Preview"
  personal_site: "Personal Site"
  best_summarize_your_sign_language: "Best summarize your sign language"
  personal_experience: "Personal experience"
  save: "Save"
  email_alert_settings: "E-mail alert settings"
  be_concerned: "Be concerned"
  to_answer_the_concerns_of_a_new: "To answer the concerns of a new"
  i_was_invited_to_answer_questions: "I was invited to answer questions"
  some_people_have_asked_me: "Some people have asked me"
  delete_my_account: "Delete My Account"
  do_not_like: "Do not like"
  delete_this_account: "Delete this account"
  can_not_recover_deleted: "Can not recover deleted"
  are_you_sure_you: "Are you sure you"
  join_the_community: "Join the community"
  how_to_registered_users: "How to Registered Users"
  to_control_the_quality_of_community_content: "To control the quality of community content"
  invite_others_to_join_must: "Invite others to join must"
  you_can_use_your_social_resources: "You can use your social resources"
  invite_you_to_find_other_people: "Invite you to find other people"
  or_send_your_personal_data_to: "Or send your personal data to"
  after_we_review: "After we review"
  if_you_meet_the_requirements: "If you meet the requirements"
  will_send_you: "Will send you"
  invitation_link: "Invitation link"
  therefore: "Therefore,"
  please_try_to_describe_yourself: "Please try to describe yourself"
  new_user_registration: "New user registration"
  provisional_registration_period_is_currently_open: "Provisional registration period is currently open"
  if_you_have_not: "If don't have a "
  account_then: " Account, then"
  hurry_up_now: "Hurry up now"
  name: "Name"
  can_not_be_changed_after_registration: "Can not be changed after registration"
  password: "Password"
  remember_me: "Remember Me"
  confirm_password: "Confirm Password"
  submit_registration_information: "Submit registration information"
  about_registration: "About Registration"
  itself_can_be_invited_to_register: "Itself can be invited to register"
  but_we_will_occasionally_some_special_days_in_the_temporary_open_up: "But we will occasionally some special days in the temporary open up"
  if_you_see_this_page: "If you see this page"
  congratulations_you: "Congratulations, you"
  department_can_not_submit_the_issue_lead_to: "Department can not submit the issue lead to"
  login_account_with_other_platforms: "Login account with other platforms"
  douban: "Douban"
  tencent_microblogging: "Tencent microblogging"
  sina_microblogging: "Sina microblogging"
  netease_account: "NetEase account"
  sohu_account: "Sohu account"
  is_bound: "Is bound"
  edit_image: "Edit image"
  modify_the_topic_image: "Modify the topic image"
  local_upload: "Local upload"
  support: "Support"
  picture_format: "Picture format"
  do_not_exceed: "Do not exceed"
  recommended_image_size_is_larger_than: "Recommended image size is larger than"
  people_concerned_about_this_topic_recently: "People concerned about this topic recently"
  upload_failed: "Upload failed"
  format_problem: "Format problem"
  you_can_click_on_the_link_below_to_access_this_page: "You can click on the link below to access this page"
  on: "On"
  he_has: "He has"
  question: "Question"
  concerned_about_the: "Concerned about the"
  invite_you_to_answer_this_question: "Invite you to answer this question"
  you_can_click_on_the_link_below_and_answer_this_question: "You can click on the link below and answer this question"
  you_have_successfully_registered_as_a: "You have successfully registered as a"
  members: "Members"
  who_also_is_still_in: "Who also is still in"
  stage: "Stage"
  we_are_trying_to_improve_it: "We are trying to improve it"
  if_there_are_issues_that_a_lot_of_understanding: "If there are issues that a lot of understanding"
  feedback_and_suggestions_can_be_sent_to: "Feedback and suggestions can be sent to"
  or_can_be_submitted_directly_to_the: "Or can be submitted directly to the"
  have_not_had_time_to_write_his_personal_introduction: "Have not had time to write his personal introduction"
  modify_personal_experience: "Modify my bio."
  home: "Home"
  asked: "Asked"
  answered: "Answered"
  on: "On"
  questions: "Questions"
  add_a_description_of_the_problem: "Add a description of the problem"
  problem_description: "Problem Description"
  this_is_your_own: "This is your own"
  after_logging_you_can_focus: "After logging you can focus"
  registered_in: "Registered in"
  recent_attention: "Recent attention"
  recent_attention_to_the_people: "Recent attention to the people"
  
  
  ##############################################################################################
  
  

  
  date:
    formats:
      default: "% Y-% m-% d"
      short: "% b% d days"
      long: "% Y% b% d day of"
    day_names: [Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday]
    abbr_day_names: [Sun, Mon, Tue, Wed, Thu, Fri, Sat]
    month_names: [~, January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November, December]
    abbr_month_names: [~, Jan, Feb, Mar, Apr, May, Jun, Jul, Aug, Sept, Oct, Nov, Dec]
    order: [:year, :month, :day]
  
  time:
    formats:
      default: "% Y% b% d day of% A% H:% M:% S% Z"
      short: "% b% d at% H:% M"
      long: "% Y% b% d day of% H:% M"
      min: "% H:% M"
    am: "am"
    pm: "pm"
  
  datetime:
    distance_in_words:
      half_a_minute: "half a minute"
      less_than_x_seconds:
        one: "less than one second"
        other: "Less than %{count} seconds"
      x_seconds:
        one: "one second"
        other: " %{count} seconds"
      less_than_x_minutes:
        one: "less than a minute"
        other: "Less than %{count} minutes"
      x_minutes:
        one: "One Minute"
        other: " %{count} minutes"
      about_x_hours:
        one: "About an hour"
        other: "about %{count} hours"
      x_days:
        one: "one day"
        other: " %{count} days"
      about_x_months:
        one: "About a month"
        other: "about %{count} months"
      x_months:
        one: "one month"
        other: " %{count} months"
      about_x_years:
        one: "About a year"
        other: "In about %{count}"
      over_x_years:
        one: "one year"
        other: " %{count} years"
      almost_x_years:
        one: "for nearly a year"
        other: "In close to %{count}"
    prompts:
      year: "Year"
      month: "Month"
      day: "Day"
      hour: "Hour"
      minute: "Minutes"
      second: "Seconds"
  
  number:
    format:
      separator: "."
      delimiter: ","
      precision: 3
    currency:
      format:
        format: "% u% n"
        unit: "CN ¥"
        separator: "."
        delimiter: ","
        precision: 2
    percentage:
      format:
        delimiter: ""
    precision:
      format:
        delimiter: ""
    human:
      format:
        delimiter: ""
        precision: 1
      storage_units:
        format: "% n% u"
        units:
          byte:
            one: "Byte"
            other: "Bytes"
          kb: "KB"
          mb: "MB"
          gb: "GB"
          tb: "TB"
  
  support:
    array:
      words_connector: ","
      two_words_connector: "and"
      last_word_connector: ", and"
    select:
      prompt: "Select"
  
  activemodel:
    errors:
      template: # ~ 2.3.5 backward compatible
        header:
          one: "there is an error, %{model} can not be saved. "
          other: "there are %{count} errors, %{model} can not be saved. "
        body: "the following fields are invalid:"
      messages:
        inclusion: "is not included in the list"
        exclusion: "is a reserved keyword"
        invalid: "is invalid"
        confirmation: "and confirm the value does not match"
        accepted: "must be accepted"
        empty: "can not be empty"
        blank: "can not be null"
        too_long: "is too long (up to %{count} characters)"
        too_short: "is too short (minimum is %{count} characters)"
        wrong_length: "Illegal length (must be a %{count} characters)"
        taken: "has been used"
        not_a_number: "is not a number"
        not_an_integer: "must be an integer"
        greater_than: "must be greater than %{count}"
        greater_than_or_equal_to: "must be greater than or equal to %{count}"
        equal_to: "must be equal to %{count}"
        less_than: "must be less than %{count}"
        less_than_or_equal_to: "must be less than or equal to %{count}"
        odd: "must be singular"
        even: "must be a two-number"
        record_invalid: "validation failed: %{errors}"
    models:
      user: "Users"
      topic: "Topics"
      ask: "Issues"
      answer: "Answers"
    attributes:
      user:
        name: "name"
        slug: "personal url slug"
        email: "Email"
        bio: "Bio"
        password: "password"
        password_confirmation: "Confirm password"
        website: "Your Website"
        avatar: "Avatar"
        last_logined_at: "Last Login Time"
        tagline: "signature"
      topic:
        title: "Title"
      ask:
        title: "Title"
  
  activemodel:
    errors:
      template:
        header:
          one: "there is an error occurs that causes %{model} can not be saved. "
          other: "there are %{count} error occurs that causes %{model} can not be saved. "
        body: "the following fields appear in the error:"
          
  mongoid:
    errors:
      models:
        user: User
      messages:
        inclusion: "is not included in the list"
        exclusion: "is reserved keyword"
        invalid: "is invalid"
        confirmation: "and confirm the value does not match"
        accepted: "must be accepted"
        empty: "can not be empty"
        blank: "can not be null"
        too_long: "too long (up to %{count} characters)"
        too_short: "is too short (minimum is %{count} characters)"
        wrong_length: "Illegal length (must be a %{count} characters)"
        taken: "has been used"
        not_a_number: "not a number"
        not_an_integer: "must be an integer"
        greater_than: "must be greater than %{count}"
        greater_than_or_equal_to: "must be greater than or equal to %{count}"
        equal_to: "must be equal to %{count}"
        less_than: "must be less than %{count}"
        less_than_or_equal_to: "must be less than or equal to %{count}"
        odd: "must be odd"
        even: "must be even"
        record_invalid: "validation failed: %{errors}"
        document_not_found:
          "Found no class is %{klass} ID is the document %{identifiers}"
        invalid_database:
          "Database should be Mongo::DB, rather than %{name}."
        invalid_type:
          "In the class %{klass} is defined in a field, the actual value is %{value} of %{other}."
        unsupported_version:
          "MongoDB %{version} version has expired, please upgrade to %{mongo_version}."
        validations:
          "Validation failed - %{errors}."
        invalid_collection:
          "Does not allow direct access to the embedded set %{klass}, root access from the document collection."
        invalid_field:
          "Field name does not allow for %{name}. You should not define the internal property or method with Mongoid the same name, see detailed Use Document # instance_methods."
        too_many_nested_attribute_records:
          "Was associated with %{association} embedded property can not exceed %{limit}."
        embedded_in_must_have_inverse_of:
          "embedded_in association property must contain inverse_of."
        dependent_only_references_one_or_many:
          "dependent => destroy | delete option is only valid when the references_one or references_many."
        association_cant_have_inverse_of:
          "In the current association does not allow to define inverse_of, the only embedded_in or references_many an array of circumstances under"
        unsaved_document:
          "You cannot call create or create! Through a relational association
          relation ( %{document}) who's parent ( %{base}) is not already saved."